The PIMBOC Guide, Processes and
Communication Management.
So in initiating process group,
again referring back to the process map on
page 25 of your PIMBAC, we have no
processes.
In planning, of course,
we'll plan communication
management early on along
with stakeholder engagement.
Who needs what, when, where, why,
how.
So those are unbelievably intertwined.
We often do them together.
Executing, we'll manage communications.
This is where we will actually be
communicating, sending out reports in the
project communications, and all the while,
monitoring and controlling, making sure
the information needs of the stakeholders
are actually being met.